Are you a tea drinker?
你是一名茶饮爱好者吗？
If so, you’re not alone.
如果是的话，你并不是一个人。
Every day around the world millions of cups of this popular brew are drunk, and it’s been that way for thousands of years.
在全球范围内，每天都有上百万杯这种广受欢迎的饮品被人们饮用，这样的习惯已经延续了数千年。
The oldest discovered tea is from the Han Dynasty, dating from 206BC to 220AD.
目前发现的最古老的茶叶来自公元前206年至公元220年的汉朝。
But it’s thought that the tea trend really took off during the Tang Dynasty in the 8th Century, when it became China’s national drink.
但人们认为，饮茶的风潮真正盛行起来是在公元8世纪的唐朝，当时茶成了中国的国饮。
Now, Turkey, the Republic of Ireland and the UK are believed to be the biggest tea-drinking nations, per capita.
如今，土耳其、爱尔兰共和国和英国被认为是全球人均饮茶量最高的国家。
Tea is consumed in many ways – slurped, sipped or glugged.
茶的饮用方式多种多样——可大口啜饮、小口抿饮，也可豪饮。
It can be poured from pots, infused or brewed in the cup using tea bags – and it’s this latter process that is causing concern.
茶可以从茶壶中倒出饮用，也可以用茶包在杯中冲泡——而正是这后一种冲泡方式引发了人们的担忧。
Research last year found some premium tea bags might be leaving billions of microscopic plastic particles in the cup.
去年的一项研究发现，一些高端茶包可能会在杯中留下数十亿个微小的塑料颗粒。
Scientists from McGill University in Montreal found that some ‘plastic’ tea bags shed high levels of microplastics into water.
蒙特利尔麦吉尔大学的科学家们发现，一些“塑料材质”的茶包会向水中释放大量微塑料。
However, The World Health Organization says such particles in drinking water do not appear to pose a risk.
不过，世界卫生组织表示，饮用水中的这类塑料颗粒似乎并不会构成健康威胁。
Most tea bags are made from paper, with a small amount of plastic used to seal them shut – made from oil.
大多数茶包的材质是纸，会使用少量以石油为原料制成的塑料来封口。
This has led to debate about whether they can be recycled, but many are still composted.
这引发了关于茶包能否回收利用的争论，但许多茶包仍会被用于堆肥。
However, gardener Mike Armitage has told the BBC that the plastic contained in the soil could be washed into streams and rivers and ultimately out to sea.
不过，园丁迈克·阿米蒂奇向英国广播公司表示，混入土壤中的塑料可能会被冲刷到小溪和河流中，最终流入大海。
Unilever, the owners of the tea brand PG Tips, said their tea bags are made with a small amount of plastic – used to seal them – and that they are suitable for composting.
联合利华集团是茶饮品牌PG Tips的母公司，该集团表示，旗下茶包仅使用少量塑料用于封口，且这些茶包适合堆肥处理。
And the brand Yorkshire Tea said their bags do contain 25% polypropylene, but they were “actively developing plant-based and biodegradable alternatives”.
约克郡茶品牌则称，其茶包确实含有25%的聚丙烯成分，但该品牌“正在积极研发植物基且可生物降解的替代品”。
While tea bag manufacturers might be doing their bit to reduce plastic pollution, it could be a good time to switch your favourite beverage to coffee, or if that isn’t your cup of tea then try using loose-leaf tea, which can have a better flavour.
尽管茶包制造商们在为减少塑料污染尽自己的一份力，但或许现在是时候把你最爱的饮品换成咖啡了；如果你对咖啡不感兴趣，那么不妨试试散装茶叶，它的口感会更好。